The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
My Thunder Celestial Grand Formation
shall be
completed today !
The formation isn't complete,
but space is already on the verge of collapse.
If this formation is completed,
the Thunder Celestial Realm will become a dead area.
I can't escape.
For now, I'll just have to improvise.
The origin energy of this man
is shaking half of the Celestial Realm fragments.
What's his cultivation level ?
Refining the Celestial Realm into an artifact ?
Not a bad idea.
But without a formation spirit to anchor it,
it's nothing but a pile of slightly large rocks.
Celestial Lord,
have a look at that !
Formation spirits...
Appear !
They're all Origin Souls of Illusory Yin cultivators !?
28 souls,
merge !
A mere rank 4 Upper Celestial ?
How embarrassing...
Celestial Lord, wait a moment.
Formation spirits, appear again !
Given his strength,
killing over a dozen Corporeal Yang cultivators to take their souls
isn't difficult.
Rank 9 Upper Celestial ?
It's nothing special.
Appear again !
This aura rivals that of the Huan Family Ancestor !
It must be a Nirvana Scryer cultivator !
Rank 3 Sky Celestial ?
It's passable.
This one
is somewhat interesting.
A rank 9 Sky Celestial.
What a pity,
he was the fourth person fated with me.
This person's cultivation...
I can't see through it.
A prodigy of this caliber
is only good enough to be used as a formation spirit ?
What are you roaring about ?
A rank 2 Celestial King...
Fifth soul,
get into position !
Remember your promise.
Blood Ancestor !
Fourth soul,
get into position !
Using a rank 6 Celestial King as a formation spirit
is quite a feat.
Do you have
a Celestial Lord ?
Of course.
This pressure...
I've only felt it from the All-Seer !
Such extraordinary experts
were also soul-extracted and refined into formation spirits !
Rank 1 Celestial Lords of the Thunder Celestial Realm !
Third soul, second soul,
get into position !
One last one remains.
Just its killing intent
is enough to shake the world !
The rank 6 Slaughter Celestial Lord of the Rain Celestial Realm
has also fallen into your hands.
First soul,
get into position.
Celestial Formation,
activate !
This formation now has world-destroying power...
But why did Master Flamespark
go through the trouble of luring Qing Shui here ?
Nice formation.
Although this Celestial Formation is powerful,
it still lacks sharpness.
I understand now why you're after me.
That's correct.
I invited you here
precisely so you can help me
to complete the Celestial Formation with your Ji Realm !
May I ask Celestial Lord Qing Shui
what you think of this ?
I told you before
that I'm not Qing Shui !
It seems your memory
has been sleeping within the seal for too long...
But today,
I shall use this Celestial Descent Platform
to help you remember !
This old man has been to the Celestial Realm hundreds of times
and read countless ancient jades
until I found this one !
What this jade slip records
is precisely the life of Celestial Emperor Bai Fan's disciple,
Celestial Lord Qing Shui.
Your name is Qing Shui.
You were a crown prince in the ancient cultivation world, in the Clear Water State.
When you ascended to the Celestial Realm back then,
you came to this very place,
the Celestial Descent Platform.
And it was also here
that you met Celestial Emperor Bai Fan
and were taken as his disciple.
During the next tens of thousands of years,
you followed Bai Fan in campaigns across the lands
to expand his territory.
You brought honor to your family.
How glorious it was...
But overnight,
Dear ! What's wrong with you ?
You lost your mind
and fell to a demonic possession.
Everyone around you
died by your hand.
You possessed the Ji Realm,
so naturally, no one could stand against you.
You slaughtered countless people.
That's how
you brought about the most tragic calamity
since the creation of the Thunder Celestial Realm.
Then your master,
Celestial Emperor Bai Fan, personally arrived,
and helpd you regain your senses.
But the damage had already been done.
Yan'er !
No...
Impossible...
Yan'er,
wake up.
It's me,
I'm back.
Yan'er !
Nooo !!!
That day,
you split your own body apart in your despair,
and sealed it with artifacts
to condemn yourself to never be reborn.
Bai Fan couldn't bear it,
so he placed a healing formation outside the seals
in hope that you would awaken one day.
If you help me to complete this formation,
I will find the cause of your demonic possession.
After that,
you'll be able to avenge your loved ones !
He gathered formation spirits,
raised Thunder Beasts,
and refined the Celestial Realm...
To make Qing Shui help him,
he investigated for tens of thousands of years.
This man's behavior seems crazy
but in reality, every move he makes
is planned meticulously.
Enough !
Qing Shui,
I've helped you recover your memories
out of good will !
What do you mean by this ?
Could he...
have been overtaken by his demonic thoughts once again ?
That shouldn't be possible.
I had finally forgotten...
Why did you...
have to remind me ?
Call the Wind !
Celestial Formation, assemble origin !
This is...
the true power of Call the Wind !
Celestial Lord Qing Shui,
do you know
that not long after you were sealed,
your master Bai Fan died under mysterious circumstances
and the Thunder Celestial Realm collapsed soon after ?
Don't you want to...
Shut up !
Summon the Rain !
Ice Seal !
After Call the Wind
comes Summon the Rain.
The Celestial Emperor's spells
are truly extraordinary.
Qing Shui,
Your best choice is to join forces with me.
You and I are not enemies.
Don't refuse my kind offer only to end up with a worse one !
You need to restore your cultivation
and require a massive amount of origin energy.
Come with me to the Alliance Star System
and devour strong cultivators there.
With my help,
your cultivation will soon return to its peak !
That reason
isn't enough !
As expected...
Just some residual energy
is enough to take my life.
I found that when you fell into demonic possession back then,
someone in the Rain Celestial Realm also suffered the same fate.
If you help me,
I will provide you with the clues and the survivors !
Not enough !
The Cultivation Alliance has a scroll within its archives
that surfaced shortly after the Celestial Realm collapsed.
This item is deeply connected to the destruction of the Celestial Realm !
Your demonic possession,
Bai Fan's death,
and the fall of the Celestial Realm
have all been orchestrated by the same thing !
Don't you want to uncover the truth
and avenge your loved one ?
If you lied to me,
I will detonate the Ji Realm
and reduce this formation
to dust.
Celestial Lord can rest assured,
this old man
is not lying !
Celestial Lord, come with me
to meet my friends in the Allheaven Star System.
And then,
we will open a passage
straight to the Alliance Star System
and turn it upside down !
Senior, please wait !
Congratulations on completing the formation.
Could you give Junior
his Thunder Beast back ?
I still need your Thunder Beast for a few more days.
After I open the passage to the Alliance,
I will return it to you.
Little guy,
you are fated with me.
If you can leave the Thunder Celestial Realm safely,
take this token to the Thunder Celestial Temple
and I will grant you another fortuitous opportunity.
Since you have learned Call the Wind,
you still count as my master's disciple.
Remember,
this spell is one of the 6 great spells he created.
Don't let it gather dust in your hands.
The Celestial Realm Gate was destroyed.
There is only one way
to leave this place.
To enter and exit the Thunder Celestial Realm
apart from the Celestial Gate,
there are ancient teleportation formations controlled by the Thunder Celestial Temple.
I have
placed their location within my Dao Soul
so Master can use them if needed.
The State of Clear Water is an important part of in the lore of the Er Gen universe. For instance, it's heavily referenced in I Shall Seal the Heavens. They added in a lot of details in the scenes of this episode which is a very nice touch !\N\NClear Water is the literal translation of Qing Shui. For simplicity's sake, we will refer to the character as Qing Shui and his country as Clear Water.
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.